https://taiyocircuitautomation.com/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
TAIYO CIRCUIT AUTOMATION, INC. (“We” or “Our”) understands that personal information is an important asset in society. We also recognize that the correct treatment of personal information is one of Our important obligations and hereby declare that We will endeavor to protect personal information based on the following policy:
1. Compliance with laws and regulations related to personal
information
We will treat personal information appropriately and comply with laws, regulations, and rules related to the protection of personal information.
2. Acquisition of personal information
We will obtain personal information by fair and appropriate means, and when obtaining personal information, We will endeavor to make clear the uses to which such information will be put.
3. Use of personal information
We will use acquired personal information within an extent necessary for the performance of Our duties, and within an extent reasonably related to the purposes indicated at the time such information was acquired. When using personal information in conjunction with third parties and when entrusting the treatment of personal information to third parties, We will supervise such third parties to ensure the appropriate use of personal information.
4. Provision of personal information to third parties
Except when legally stipulated, We will not provide third parties with personal information without first obtaining the prior consent of those concerned.
5. Disclosure, correction, and deletion of personal information
In the event that those concerned request that We confirm, correct, update, or delete their personal information, We will respond as necessary to a reasonable extent.
6. Personal Information Protection Regulations
The appropriate protection of personal information will be conducted in accordance with this policy, by separately stipulated Personal Information Protection Regulations.
7. Supplementary provisions
This policy will come into effect as of July 4, 2020.
Taiyo Circuit Automation, Inc. © 2020 All Rights Reserved.
